naja.co 2016-06-16

# Privacy Policy | Naja

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Effective as of November 25, 2013**

We at Black Cashmere Labs,Inc. (d/b/a Naja) (“Naja,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) have created this privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) because we know that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of Naja in connection with our online services (the “Services”), which are made available to you through www.naja.co (the “Website”), Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and other social media (collectively, “Social Media”), and through cell phones, personal digital assistants, and other mobile devices (collectively, the “Mobile Devices”). The Website, our Social Media pages, and the Mobile Devices are collectively referred to as the “Platforms.”

By visiting our Website and/or using our Services on any of the Platforms, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use.

Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Use.

When you sign up to become a Registered User, receive our newsletter, or enter any promotion or sweepstakes, you will be required to provide us with personal information about yourself (collectively, the “Personal Information”). Such Personal Information for Registered Users includes your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address. We do not collect any Personal Information from you when you use the Services unless you provide us with the Personal Information voluntarily.

When you order products and services from us, you will be required to provide certain information in addition to the Personal Information noted above. Such information may include a debit card number, credit card number, and similar information (collectively, the “Billing Information).

In order to provide the Services while you are using a Mobile Device, we may, at your consent, automatically collect geolocational information from your Mobile Device, your wireless carrier, or certain third-party service providers (“Geolocational Information”). Collection of such Geolocational Information occurs only when the Services are running on your Mobile Device. You may decline to allow us to collect such Geolocational Information, in which case Naja will not be able to provide certain Services to you. Because your Geolocational Information is subject to abuse by others, please be sure to manage your Mobile Device and privacy preferences on the Services on an ongoing basis.

In addition to the Personal Information noted above that you voluntarily provide to us, we may collect additional information (collectively, the “Other Information”). Such Other Information may include:

Additional information about yourself that you voluntarily provide to us, such as your hobbies, personal interests, household income range, number of children, gender, and product and service preferences.

Information that we automatically collect when you use the Services, such as the type of Platform you’re using, your IP addresses, browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Websites you visit, and similar information concerning your use of the Services.

Information that we collect using “cookie” technology. Cookies are small packets of data that a website stores on your computer’s hard drive so that your computer will “remember” information about your visit. We use cookies to help us collect Other Information and to enhance your experience using the Services. If you do not want the Platforms to place a cookie on your hard drive, you may be able to turn that feature off on your computer or Mobile Device. Please consult your Internet browser’s documentation for information on how to do this. However, if you decide not to accept cookies from us, the Services may not function properly. When the Services are made available to you through Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and/or other third-party Social Media sites, please be aware that these other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of information. You are responsible for reviewing those policies.

Information that we collect or receive from other sources, such as companies that provide our Services by way of a co-branded or private-labeled website (“Partner Companies”), and platforms like Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and/or other third-party Social Media sites on which you have used the Services in accordance with their terms of use and privacy policies. We may add this information to the information we may have already collected from you via our Platforms in order to improve the products and services we provide.

We may share Other Information about your activity on the Platforms with third parties for the purpose of tailoring, analyzing, managing, reporting, and optimizing advertising you see on the Platforms and elsewhere. These third parties may use cookies, pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs), and/or other technologies to collect such Other Information for such purposes. Pixel tags enable us, and these third-party advertisers, to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits the site on which the pixel tag is located in order to learn which advertisement brings a user to a given site.

If you have registered for the Services, you may access, review, and make changes to your Personal Information by (i) e-mailing us at privacy@naja.co, or (ii) following the instructions found on the applicable Platform. In addition, you may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of any Naja marketing email. Registered Users cannot opt out of receiving transactional e-mails related to their account. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to process such requests in a timely manner. You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to completely remove or modify information in our subscription databases.

We use Personal Information and Other Information to provide you the Services, solicit your feedback, inform you about our products and services and those of our third-party marketing partners, to administer our contests, and to improve our Services to you. Also, we may share Personal Information and/or Other Information as described below.

  * In order to administer our contests, we may share your Personal Information and Other Information with our third-party promotional and marketing partners.
  * We may from time to time share Personal Information and/or Other Information with other companies who may provide you information about the products and services they offer. However, to the extent required by law, you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of such sharing.
  * In an ongoing effort to better understand our users and our Services, we might analyze the Other Information in aggregate form in order to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Services. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our products and Services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.
  * We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include providing marketing assistance, information technology support, and customer service. These other companies will have access to the Personal Information and the Other Information only as necessary to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law.
  * If we or all or substantially all of our assets are acquired, we expect that Personal Information and Other Information would be transferred along with the other business assets.
  * To the extent permitted by law, we may also disclose Personal Information and Other Information when required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency, or whenever we believe that disclosing the such Information is necessary or advisable, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of Naja or others.

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect Personal Information and Other Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We use industry-standard SSL (“Secure Socket Layer”) encryption technology, a secure server, and other physical and procedural safeguards to protect the security of such information. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. In particular, e-mail sent to or from Platforms may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.

The Websites and the Services are operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using the Services and/or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer.

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 through the Services. If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide Personal Information through the Services. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents who have an established business relationship with Naja may choose to opt out of our sharing your Personal Information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and (1) you wish to opt out; or (2) you wish to request certain information regarding our disclosure of your Personal Information to third parties for the direct marketing purposes, please send an e-mail to [privacy@naja.co](mailto:privacy@naja.co) or write to us at:

Naja  
1010 Wilshire Blvd Suite 404  
Los Angeles, CA 90017

The Websites and the Services may contain links to third-party websites. Naja has no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors, or other websites to which we provide links. As such, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those third-party websites. You should check the applicable third-party privacy policy and terms of use when visiting any other websites.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any changes on the Websites as soon as they go into effect. By accessing the Websites or using the Services after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [privacy@naja.co](mailto:privacy@naja.co) or call us at 866-LOVE-NAJA.
